A Guide to the Warren Weaver papers FA419
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Reprints, 1920-1987; 1933-1977; 12; 6 Cubic Feet
  - Works by Warren Weaver, 1
    - Works by Warren Weaver, 1961 (Box 55, Folder 487)
      - Christianity and Crisis: Statistical Morality, 1961 January 23 (Box 55, Folder 487)
      - Public Health Reports: Quarter Century in the Natural Sciences, 1961 January (Box 55, Folder 487)
      - American Scientist: The Imperfections of Science, 1961 March (Box 55, Folder 487)
      - Nutrition Reviews: Why is Science Important, 1961 March (Box 55, Folder 487)
      - Think: Probability: The Odds are High that It Effects You, 1961 April (Box 55, Folder 487)
      - Science of Mind: A Scientist Ponders Faith, 1961 July (Box 55, Folder 487)
      - Academy of Religion and Mental Health: Speech at First Annual Dinner, 1961 October 26 (Box 55, Folder 487)
      - Drexel, Seventh Anniversary Convocation: Science, Learning, and the Whole of Life, 1961 December 3-5 (Box 55, Folder 487)
      - Year Book of the American Philosophical Society: Chester Irving Barnard, 1961 (Box 55, Folder 487)
    - Works by Warren Weaver, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 488)
      - Christianity and Crisis: Statistical Morality, 1961 January 23 (Box 56, Folder 488)
      - Public Health Reports: Quarter Century in the Natural Sciences, 1961 January (Box 56, Folder 488)
      - American Scientist: The Imperfections of Science, 1961 March (Box 56, Folder 488)
      - Nutrition Reviews: Why is Science Important, 1961 March (Box 56, Folder 488)
      - Think: Probability: The Odds are High that It Effects You, 1961 April (Box 56, Folder 488)
      - Science of Mind: A Scientist Ponders Faith, 1961 July (Box 56, Folder 488)
      - Academy of Religion and Mental Health: Speech at First Annual Dinner, 1961 October 26 (Box 56, Folder 488)
      - Drexel, Seventh Anniversary Convocation: Science, Learning, and the Whole of Life, 1961 December 3-5 (Box 56, Folder 488)
      - Year Book of the American Philosophical Society: Chester Irving Barnard, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 488)
    - Works by Warren Weaver, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 489)
      - Fourfront: Cancer Research: Where Are We?, 1962 February (Box 56, Folder 489)
      - Journal of Medical Education: Private Universities and the New Unity of Learning, 1962 February (Box 56, Folder 489)
      - Address given at the Congregational Church, New Milford, CT: Science and Religion, 1962 May 8 (Box 56, Folder 489)
      - Foundation News (Bulletin of Foundation Library Center): Thoughts on Philanthropy and Philanthropoids, 1962 May (Box 56, Folder 489)
      - Science (Editorial): New Institute for Biological Studies at San Diego, 1962 June 1 (Box 56, Folder 489)
      - Thoughts on the Fourth Morning, 1962 June 28 (Box 56, Folder 489)
      - New Scientist: What a Layman Needs to Know About Science (Drafted by John Lear, from material written by WW), 1962 June (Box 56, Folder 489)
      - Saturday Review: What a Moon Ticket Will Buy, 1962 August 4 (Box 56, Folder 489)
      - Houston Chronicle: Science for Everybody, 1962 September 16 (Box 56, Folder 489)
      - Science: Stability and Change, 1962 September 28 (Box 56, Folder 489)
      - Industrial Management Magazine: Probability: The Odds are High that It Effects You, 1962 September (Box 56, Folder 489)
      - Look: Christmas in Crisis, 1962 December 31 (Box 56, Folder 489)
      - Southern Research Institute: An Address, 1962 April 4 (Box 56, Folder 489)
      - Annals of the Japan Association for Philosophy of Science: The Emerging Unity of Science, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 489)
    - Works by Warren Weaver, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 490)
      - Mathematics in the United States, 1963 February 1 (Box 56, Folder 490)
      - Academy Reporter (Academy of Religion and Mental Health): A Mathematicians Prayer, 1963 February (Box 56, Folder 490)
      - Think: The New Biology, 1963 February (Box 56, Folder 490)
      - The Salk Institute for Biological Studies: Speech given a Biltmore Hotel, N.Y., 1963 May 6 (Box 56, Folder 490)
      - University of Wisconsin (Van Vleck Hall Dedication): Edward Burr Van Vleck, 1963 May (Box 56, Folder 490)
      - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists: Dreams and Responsibilities, 1963 May (Box 56, Folder 490)
      - Remarks on Retirement, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 490)
    - Works by Warren Weaver, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 491)
      - Science, 1964 March 20 (Box 56, Folder 491)
      - Science: Scientific Explanation, 1964 May 20 (Box 56, Folder 491)
      - Biographical Memoirs: Max Mason, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 491)
    - Works by Warren Weaver, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 492)
      - The American Mathematical Monthly: Award for Distinguished Service to Professor Richard Courant, 1965 January (Box 56, Folder 492)
      - The Private Library: The "India Alice", 1965 January (Box 56, Folder 492)
      - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation: Mathematics and Philanthropy, 1965 Spring (Box 56, Folder 492)
      - U.S. News and World Report: Billions for Science: Is it Worth the Price?, 1965 December 6 (Box 56, Folder 492)
      - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation: Careers in Science, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 492)
      - Science Reporter: The Kalinga Prize 1964, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 492)
    - Works by Warren Weaver, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 493)
      - Tennessee Teacher: Four Pieces of Advice to Young Peoples, 1966 January (Box 57, Folder 493)
      - The UNESCO Courier: The Inner Nature of Science, 1966 January (Box 57, Folder 493)
      - Science: Good Teaching, 1966 March (Box 57, Folder 493)
      - Saturday Review: Confessions of a Scientist-Humanist, 1966 May 28 (Box 57, Folder 493)
      - Zygon: Some Moral Problems posed by Modern Science, 1966 September (Box 57, Folder 493)
      - Address to the Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1966 October 25 (Box 57, Folder 493)
      - Pediatrics: Probability, Rarity, Interest and Surprise, 1966 October (Box 57, Folder 493)
      - Impact: L'importance de la Vulgarization Scientifique (Why is it so Important that Science be Understood?), 1966 (Box 57, Folder 493)
      - Impact: Why is it so Important that Science be Understood?, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 493)
    - Works by Warren Weaver, 1967-1969 (Box 57, Folder 494)
      - Scientific Research: Matter of Opinion, 1967 July (Box 57, Folder 494)
      - Redbook: Science and the Goodness of God, 1967 December (Box 57, Folder 494)
      - Ordo: Wissenchaft Und Komplexitat, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 494)
      - Unpublished: Where Do We Go From Here?, 1969 June (Box 57, Folder 494)
      - Saturday Review: Basic Research and the Common Good, 1969 August 9 (Box 57, Folder 494)
    - Works by Warren Weaver, 1970-1977 (Box 57, Folder 495)
      - The Library Chronicle of the University of Texas: In Pursuit of Lewis Carroll, 1970 November (Box 57, Folder 495)
      - The Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America: The First Edition of Alice's Adventures in Wonderland, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 495)
      - AAAS Bulletin: Science in a Troubled Culture: A Prescription, 1972 February (Box 57, Folder 495)
      - Year Book of the American Philosophical Society: Richard Courant, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 495)
      - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation: Alfred P. Sloan, Jr. Philanthopist, 1975 October (Box 57, Folder 495)
      - Historia Mathematica: Early Support for Mathematics from Rockefeller Agencies, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 495)
      - Nineteen Plus (?) Two (?), 1970s (Box 57, Folder 495)
      - The Religion of a Scientist, 1970s (Box 57, Folder 495)
  - Works by Others, 2
    - Works by Others, 1925-1939 (Box 57, Folder 496)
      - Gruenberg, Benjamin C.: Journal of Educational Method: Scientific Education as a Defense Against Propoganda and Dogma, 1925 November (Box 57, Folder 496)
      - Sommerfeld, A.: Bulletin of the Calcutta Mathematical Society: Uber Die Hauptschnitte Eines Polydimensionalen Wurfels, 1930 (Box 57, Folder 496)
      - Gruenberg, Benjamin C.: School and Society: Hypothesis and Doctrine in Science Teaching, 1933 May 13 (Box 57, Folder 496)
      - Slichter, Charles S.: Sigma XI Quarterly: Polymaths: Technicians, Specialists and Genius, 1933 September (Box 57, Folder 496)
      - Noll, Victor H.: Teachers College Record: The Habit of Scientific Thinking, 1933 October (Box 57, Folder 496)
      - Noll, Victor H.: Teachers College Record: Teaching the Habit of Scientific Thinking, 1933 December (Box 57, Folder 496)
      - Slichter, Charles S.: School Science and Mathematics: Mathematics and Reality, 1934 March (Box 57, Folder 496)
      - Noll, Victor H.: Teachers College Record: Measuring Scientific Thinking, 1934 May (Box 57, Folder 496)
      - Scripta Mathematica: A Physicist's Second Reaction to Megenlehre, 1934 (Box 57, Folder 496)
      - Noll, Victor H.: Journal of Abnormal and Social Psychology: Measuring the Scientific Attitude, 1935 July-September (Box 57, Folder 496)
      - Levy, H.: Determinism and Man, 1935 (Box 57, Folder 496)
      - Slichter, Charles S.: American Mathematical Monthly: The Principia and the Modern Age, 1937 August-September (Box 57, Folder 496)
      - Van Vleck, J.H.: Biographical Memoirs: Charles Elwood Mendenhall, 1937 (Box 57, Folder 496)
      - Benford, Frank: Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society: The Law of Anormalous Numbers, 1938 March (Box 57, Folder 496)
      - Gruenberg, Benjamin C.: Science Education: The Scientific Temper and Social Values, 1938 March (Box 57, Folder 496)
      - Morris, Charles W.: The University of Chicago Press: Foundations of the Theory of Signs, 1938 (Box 57, Folder 496)
      - Watson, E.C.: American Physics Teacher/American Journal of Physics, Series of 75 installments: Reproductions of Prints, Drawings and Paintings of Interest in the History of Physics, 1938-1956 (Box 57, Folder 496)
      - Huxley, J.S., C.S. Webb and A.T. Best: Nature: Temporary Poikilotherm in Birds, 1939 April 22 (Box 57, Folder 496)
      - Watson, E.C.: Osiris: The Early Days of the Academie des Sciences as Portrayed in the Engravings of Sebastien Le Clerc, 1939 (Box 57, Folder 496)
    - Works by Others, 1940-1949 (Box 57, Folder 497)
      - Compton, Karl T.: The Scientific Monthly: Religion in a Scientific Era, 1940 January (Box 57, Folder 497)
      - Slichter, Charles S.: Science in a Tavern: The Side Shows of Science, 1940 (Box 57, Folder 497)
      - Slichter, Louis B.: Bulletin of the Geological Society of America: Cooling of the Earth, 1941 April 1 (Box 57, Folder 497)
      - Huxley, J.S.: Nature: Degeneration and Relict Adaptation, 1942 June 20 (Box 57, Folder 497)
      - Birkhoff, George D.: Bulletin of the American Mathematical Society: Edward Burr Van Vleck-In Memoriam, 1944 January (Box 57, Folder 497)
      - Polanyi, Michael: Philosophical Society Meeting: Science and the Modern Crisis, 1944 November 14 (Box 57, Folder 497)
      - Cossar, J., and A. Erdelyi: Admirality Computing Service: Dictionary of Laplace Transforms, Part I, 1944 (Box 57, Folder 497)
      - Polanyi, Michael: The Scientific Monthly: The Autonomy of Science, 1945 February (Box 57, Folder 497)
      - Wald, Abraham: Annals of Mathematics: Generalization of a Theorem by v. Neumann Concerning Zero Sum Two Person Games, 1945 April (Box 57, Folder 497)
      - The Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research: The Weeds and the Grass: Research for the Conquest of Cancer, 1948 (Box 57, Folder 497)
      - Dingle, Hebert: Science Progress: Science and Professor Bernal, 1949 April (Box 57, Folder 497)
      - Planck, Max: Science: The Meaning and Limits of Exact Science, 1949 September 30 (Box 57, Folder 497)
      - Shannon, C.E.: Bell System Technical Journal: Communication Theory of Secrecy Systems, 1949 October (Box 57, Folder 497)
      - Dingle, Hebert: Thinker's Digest: The Nature of Scientific Philosophy, 1949 Winter (Box 57, Folder 497)
      - Prenant, Lucie: Europe: Louis Rapkine, 1949 (Box 57, Folder 497)
    - Works by Others, 1943 (Box 58, Folder 498)
      - Langmuir, Irving: Science: The American Association for the Advancement of Science, Common Sense, and Decency, 1943 January 1 (Box 58, Folder 498)
      - Osborn, Henry Fairfield: Science: The New York Zoological Society, 1943 March 19 (Box 58, Folder 498)
      - Russell, Henry Norris: Science: Determinism and Responsibility, 1943 March 19 (Box 58, Folder 498)
      - Wilks, S.S.: Princeton University Press: Mathematical Statistics, 1943 (Box 58, Folder 498)
    - Works by Others, 1950-1951 (Box 58, Folder 499)
      - Bohr, Niels: Science: On the Notions of Causality and Complementarity, 1950 January 20 (Box 58, Folder 499)
      - Hook, Sidney: The New York Times: The Scientist in Politics, 1950 April 9 (Box 58, Folder 499)
      - Oppenheimer, Robert: Encouragement of Science, 1950 April 14 (Box 58, Folder 499)
      - Rogers, Eric M.: Science: The Chaotic University, 1950 April 21 (Box 58, Folder 499)
      - Bridgman, P.W.: The British Journal for the Philosophy of Science: The Nature of Some of Our Future Physical Concepts, 1950 April (Box 58, Folder 499)
      - Houston, W.V.: Physics Today: Phyiscs for Adventure, 1950 June (Box 58, Folder 499)
      - Huff, Darell: Harper's Weekly: How to Lie with Statistics, 1950 August (Box 58, Folder 499)
      - Fisher, R.A.: Cambridge University Press: Creative Aspects of Natural Law, 1950 November 2 (Box 58, Folder 499)
      - McCulloch, Warren S.: Tire' de Dialectica: Why the Mind is in the Head?, 1950 (Box 58, Folder 499)
      - Swann, W.F.G.: Journal of the Franklin Instutite: Science Today and Yesterday, 1951 January (Box 58, Folder 499)
      - Huxley, J.S.: Psychiatry: Knowledge, Morality and Destiny, 1951 May (Box 58, Folder 499)
      - Moe, Henry Allen: The Pacific Spectator: The Power of Freedom, 1951 Autumn (Box 58, Folder 499)
      - Redheffer, R.M.: The Annals of Mathmatical Statistics: A Note on the Surprise Index, 1951 (Box 58, Folder 499)
    - Works by Others, 1952-1953 (Box 58, Folder 500)
      - Institute for the Unity of Science (Proceedings of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences): Contributions, The Analysis and Synthesis of Knowledge, 1952 May (Box 58, Folder 500)
      - Bartlett, M.S.: Biometrika: The Statistical Significance of Odd Bits of Information, 1952 December (Box 58, Folder 500)
      - Mackay, D.M.: Proc. Arist. Soc. Suppt.: Mentality in Machines, 1952 (Box 58, Folder 500)
      - Bar-Hillel, Yehoshua: Language: A Quasi-Arithmetical Notation for Syntactic Description, 1953 January-March (Box 58, Folder 500)
      - Weis, Paul: Journal of Mount Sinai Hospital: Medicine and Society: The Biological Foundations, 1953 March-April (Box 58, Folder 500)
      - Swann, W.F.G.: The Journal of the Franklin Institute: Is the Universe Planned?, 1953 May (Box 58, Folder 500)
      - Synthese: Proceedings of the Ninth International Significant Summer Conference, 1953 August 10-15 (Box 58, Folder 500)
      - Brillouin, L.: Journal of Applied Physics: The Negentropy Principle of Information, 1953 September (Box 58, Folder 500)
      - Burks, Arthur W., and Jesse B. Wright: Proceedings of the I.R.E.: Theory of Logical Nets, 1953 October (Box 58, Folder 500)
      - Harrar, J. George: Oberlin Printing Company: Science and Human Needs, 1953 (Box 58, Folder 500)
      - Woodger, J.H.: The British Journal for the Philosophy of Science: What Do We Mean By "Inborn"?, 1953 (Box 58, Folder 500)
    - Works by Others, 1954-1955 (Box 58, Folder 501)
      - Skewes, S.: Proceedings of the London Mathematical Society: On the Difference, 1954 January 21 (Box 58, Folder 501)
      - Bar-Hillel, Yehoshua: American Scientist: Can Translation be Mechanized?, 1954 April (Box 58, Folder 501)
      - Swann, W.F.G.: Journal of the Franklin Instutite: Beauty, the Ideal of the Arts, and the Sciences, 1954 June (Box 58, Folder 501)
      - Tiselius, Arne: Journal of Chemical Study: Some Applications of the Separation of Large Molecules and Colloidal Particles, 1954 July (Box 58, Folder 501)
      - Bush, Vannevar: American Philosophical Society: Scientific Motivation, 1954 August (Box 58, Folder 501)
      - Sturtevant, A.H.: Science: Social Implications of the Genetics of Man, 1954 September 10 (Box 58, Folder 501)
      - Piel, Gerard: Scientific American: How to Write Science for the Citizen, 1954 October 12 (Box 58, Folder 501)
      - Tukey, John W.: Journal of American Statistical Association: Unsolved Problems of Experimental Statistics, 1954 (Box 58, Folder 501)
      - Muller, H.J.: Science: Genetics Damage Produced by Radiation, 1955 January 17 (Box 58, Folder 501)
      - Grant, John B.: Journal of Medical Education: Medical Regionalization and Education, 1955 February (Box 58, Folder 501)
      - Pollard, William G.: The Christian Science Scholar: An Inquiry into the Status of Non-Conceptual Experience, 1955 March (Box 58, Folder 501)
      - Bush, Vannevar: American Scientist: Science and Progress, 1955 April (Box 58, Folder 501)
      - Swann, W.F.G.: Journal of the Franklin Instutite: The Known and the Unknown, 1955 May (Box 58, Folder 501)
      - Tukey, John W.: The American Mathematical Monthly: Mathematical Consultants Computational Mathematics and Mathematical Engineering, 1955 October (Box 58, Folder 501)
      - Whyte, L.L.: The British Journal for the Philosophy of Science: One-Way Processes in Physics and Biophysics, 1955 November (Box 58, Folder 501)
      - Tukey, John W.: Biometrica: Interpolations and Approximations Related to the Normal Range, 1955 December (Box 58, Folder 501)
      - Harrison, George R.: The Atlantic Monthly: Albert Einstein, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 501)
    - Works by Others, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 502)
      - Laughlin, J.S., and I. Pullman: National Academy of Sciences: Physical Properties of Ionizing Radiations Which Affect the Population of the United States, 1956 April 18 (Box 59, Folder 502)
      - Swann, W.F.G.: Journal of the Franklin Instutite: Nature and Mind of Man, 1956 June (Box 59, Folder 502)
      - David, Herbert T.: The Annals of Mathmatical Statistics: The Wager Sequential t-Test Reaches A Decision with Probability One, 1956 September (Box 59, Folder 502)
      - Benoit, Emile: Challenge: What's Holding Back Atomic Power?, 1956 October (Box 59, Folder 502)
      - Glass, Bentley: Bulletin of Atomic Scientists: The Hazards of Atomic Radiations to Man: British and American Reports, 1956 October (Box 59, Folder 502)
      - Wheeler, John A.: American Scientist: A Septet of Sibyls: Aids in the Search for Truth, 1956 October (Box 59, Folder 502)
      - Brown, Arthur Judson: The Church Peace Union: Address (at the honor of his 100th birthday), 1956 December 3 (Box 59, Folder 502)
      - Good, I.J.: The Annals of Mathmatical Statistics: The Surprise Index for the Multivariate Normal Distribution, 1956 December (Box 59, Folder 502)
      - The Princeton University Library Chronicle, 1956 Winter (Box 59, Folder 502)
      - Slichter, Louis B.: Natural Resources: Some Aspects, Mainly Geophysical, of Mineral Exploration, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 502)
      - National Academy of Sciences (National Research Council): The Biological Effects of Atomic Radiation, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 502)
    - Works by Others, 1957 (Box 59, Folder 503)
      - Huxley, J.S.: British Medical Journal: Material of Early Contraceptive Sheaths, 1957 March 9 (Box 59, Folder 503)
      - Anderson, T.W., and Leo A. Goodman: The Annals of Mathmatical Statistics: Statistical Inference About Markov Chains, 1957 March (Box 59, Folder 503)
      - Von Bertalanffy, Ludwig: The Historical Development of Physiological Thought: Modern Concepts on Biological Adaptation, 1957 April 9 (Box 59, Folder 503)
      - Swann, W.F.G.: Journal of the Franklin Instutite: Reality, Imagery and Fantasy, 1957 May (Box 59, Folder 503)
      - Power, Edwin A. and John A. Wheeler: The Review of Modern Physics: Termal Geons, 1957 July (Box 59, Folder 503)
      - Science and Freedom: A Bulletin of the Committee on Science and Freedom: Apartheid: The Threat to South Africa's Universities, 1957 August (Box 59, Folder 503)
      - World Health Organization: Chronicle of the World Health Organization, 1957 August (Box 59, Folder 503)
      - Society of Friends: An Appeal to Scientists to Consider their Personal Responsibility for the Development of Nuclear Weapons and for Other Applications of Science to Warfare, 1957 August (Box 59, Folder 503)
      - Huxley, J.S.: Nature: Three Types of Evolutionary Process, 1957 September 7 (Box 59, Folder 503)
      - Slichter, Louis B.: Mineral Exploration, 1957 November (Box 59, Folder 503)
      - National Council of the Churches of Christ in the United States of America: International Aid and Trade, 1957 December (Box 59, Folder 503)
      - National Council of the Churches of Christ in the United States of America: Some Hopes and Concerns of the Churches in the Nuclear Space Age, 1957 December (Box 59, Folder 503)
      - Wolfowitz, J.: Illinois Journal of Mathematics: The Coding of Messages Subject to Chance Errors, 1957 December (Box 59, Folder 503)
      - Langer, Rudolph E. and Mark H. Ingraham: National Academy of Sciences: Edward Burr Van Vleck, 1957 (Box 59, Folder 503)
      - Kackler: Perspectives in Biology and Medicine: Some Considerations Regarding Biochemical Genetics in Man, 1957 Autumn (Box 59, Folder 503)
    - Works by Others, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
      - United States Government Printing Office: Hearings Before A Subcommittee of the Committee on Government Operations, United States House of Representatives, 1958 January 20-22 (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
      - Kiefer, J. and J. Wolfowitz: Transactions of the American Mathematical Society: On the Deviations of the Empiric Distribution Function of Vector Chance Variables, 1958 January (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
      - Wilks, S.S.: The Mathematics Teacher: New Fields and Organizations in the Mathematical, 1958 January (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
      - Streeter, Edward: Memorandum on Sheldon Pennoyer, 1958 February 1 (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
      - Wolfowitz, J.: Illinois Journal of Mathematics: An Upper Bound on the Rate of Transmission of Messages, 1958 March (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
      - H.W. Kuhn and A.W. Tucker: Bulletin of the American Mathematical Society: John Von Neumann's Work in the Theory of Games and Mathematical Economics, 1958 May (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
      - Good, I.J. and K. Caj Doog: Information and Control: A Paradox Concerning Rate of Information, 1958 May (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
      - Pyke, Magnus: The Listener: The Limits of Science, 1958 June 19 (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
      - Koller, P.C.: Nature: Genetic Aspect of Somantic Cell Variation, 1958 June 21 (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
      - Wolfowitz, J.: The Annals of Mathematical Statistics: Information Theory for Mathematics, 1958 June (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
      - Julian Huxley: Evolution After Darwin: The University of Chicago Centennial, University of Chicago Press: The Emergence of Darwinism, 1958 July (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
      - Muller, H.J.: Bulletin of the American Mathematical Society: Evolution by Mutation, 1958 July (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
      - Barnard, Chester I.: California Management Review: Elementary Conditions of Business Morals, 1958 Fall (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
      - Wolfowitz, J.: Illinois Journal of Mathematics: The Maximum Achievable Length of an Error Correcting Code, 1958 September (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
      - Herrick, C. Judson: Perspectives in Biology and Medicine: Science, Faith and Human Nature, 1958 Autumn (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
      - Science and Freedom (A Bulletin of the Committee on Science and Freedom), 1958 October (Box 59, Folder 504-505)
      - Shrader, James Houston. ed.: Religious Inquiry: Exploratory Studies on Emperic Approaches to Religion, 1958 October (Box 59, Folder 504-505)